I have some of this.
私は何 됲かこれを持っています
I had a lot.
私 はたくさんだった
I like having things.
私 は 何 の ものを持っているのが好きです
How many times have I had?
私は何度持っているのですか?
20 ido Awesome It's been 3 weeks for me.
20 ido すごい 私は3週間過ぎます
3 weeks soon.
すぐに3週間です
I haven't been able to wear it since it's finished or for a while
私はそれが終わったか、しばらく時からそれをまつんで着ることが
I can do it.
出来 ます
But I wonder if it's over or not.
しか し、 私はそれが終わったか、
You can worship it for a while.
しばらく時からそれをまつることが出来ます
I
私は
It's been a while since I've finished it, or I've been able to worship it for a while.
それ が終わったか、しばらく時からそれをまつることが出来
Masu.
ます
I'm a sleeping person damages Well, it's a good thing
僕 は 眠 っている人 damages そうですね 良いもの
I wish I could find it.
見 つけたらいいです
good
いい
Don't worry, just wear your underwear.
よ、 気にせんと、下着を着て
Don't you like it?
好きない?
What about the underwear you're wearing now?
今、足つけてる下着はどうなの?
Something you don't need anymore?
もういらないやつ?
It's just beautiful though.
普通に綺麗だけど
It might hurt already.
もう痛いかも
it hurts?
痛い?
Looks pitiful.
可哀しそう
Do you like anything thicker than underwear?
下着以外は何か厚めの好き?
sneakers.
スニーカー
I like sneakers.
スニーカー好き
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうだね
Nike.
ナイキー
A confession.
一番坦白
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
Even if it's surprising.
意外でも
Isn't it hair force?
ヘアフォースじゃない?
Were you playing basketball?
バスケしてたの?
I don't play basketball.
バスケしてない
I haven't done it at all.
全然してない
Nike, right?
ナイキーよね
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いよね
Yeah, it's cute.
うん、可愛い
She looks exactly like Mana-chan with her legs.
足でマナちゃんがちゃんと似てるやん
I've been told that.
言われたことある
That's what I was told.
言われたもん
Similar, similar.
似てる、似てる
Good, it's cute.
いい やん、可愛い
Hinagadakko too, you're not getting old.
ひながだっ子もね、 年取らへんね、
It's always beautiful.
ずっと美しいよね
Mana-chan too, since she was a child actress.
足でマナちゃんもね、 子役時代から、
Even now.
今でもね
be?
ある?
It's getting hot.
熱くなってくるじゃん
It's a little big.
ちょっと大きい
Is that so?
そうなの?
It's so beautiful
めちゃめちゃ綺麗で
Sho.
しょ
Can you figure it out yourself?
自 分でわかる?
Move it yourself
自分で動かしてほ
Yes.
しい
Open your butt.
お 尻開いて
Let's be careful.
気重にしよう
Did you feel better?
気持ちよくなれた?
Aren't you hungry?
お腹空いてない?
Gluttony?
大食い?
Big eater.
大食い
Are you the type of person who orders a large bowl when you go out for ramen?
ラーメンとか行ったら 大盛り頼むタイプ?
Kaela microphone type?
カエラマイクタイプ?
Hompia.
ホンピア
You can leave.
出ていいよ
I can't stop it at all.
全然止めらへん
Why don't you have a shower?
なんでシャワー持たへんの?
Right, right.
右、右
I'm hungry.
お腹減ったね
What did you come to eat?
何食べに来たんですか?
ramen.
ラーメン
What did you ask for?
何頼んだんですか?
It's painful though.
辛いけど
I'm looking forward to it.
楽しみやね
Are you looking forward to it?
楽しみに待っときますか?
This is the hardest thing ever.
この 間一番辛いよ
Let's look forward to it.
楽しみにしておこう